[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was meant by spring chickens in the early 1900s?", "correct_answer": "young male chickens", "incorrect_answers": ["old male chickens", "young female chickens", "old female chickens"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the Latin proverb Quod me nutrit me destruit, one of Angelina Jolies many tattoos?", "correct_answer": "What nourishes me destroys me", "incorrect_answers": ["Whom I feed will destroy me", "When I am naked I am vulnerable", "Who feeds me will kill me"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The dark spots on the moon that create the man in the moon image are actually basins filled with basalt.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Freddy vs. Jason, Freddy Krueger wins the battle of slasher movie icons.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Through what body part can an elephant NOT hear?", "correct_answer": "skin", "incorrect_answers": ["feet", "trunk", "ears"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal is depicted on the Coat of Arms of Norway?", "correct_answer": "Lion", "incorrect_answers": ["Bear", "Deer", "Wolf"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these animals cannot be found in North America?", "correct_answer": "Dingo", "incorrect_answers": ["Flamingo", "Walrus", "Beaver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Its not necessary to posses a point to have a point. is a quote from what 2006 movie?", "correct_answer": "The Point", "incorrect_answers": ["Animal House", "Casablanca", "We Are Marshall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the second US president?", "correct_answer": "John Adams", "incorrect_answers": ["Martin Van Buren", "James Monroe", "Thomas Jefferson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the term blood diamond?", "correct_answer": "Diamond used for financing wars", "incorrect_answers": ["Red diamond", "Stolen diamond", "Diamond for which somebody has died"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Death Penalty for murder was abolished in the United Kingdom in 1965.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name given to the current model of a cell membrane?", "correct_answer": "Fluid Mosaic model", "incorrect_answers": ["Bilayer Phospholipid model", "Davson-Danielli model", "Protein-Lipid model"]}]